driversleuth.com 2015-04-20

# Privacy Policy | Driver Sleuth

The terms below discloses the privacy policy for the website DriverSleuth.com and applies only to the information collected by this site. By accessing the site and downloading any software from DriverSleuth.com you are bound by these website terms and conditions. We are very serious about your privacy and have no intention of selling your information for any reason. 

## Collected Information

We collect your personal information to further assist our company in delivering a high level customer service and experience when interacting on our website. Non-identifiable data such as your time on the site, pages that you visit, and IP address help us deliver the best user experience that we can offer. Personal information is only collected by forms on the website and never without your knowledge. This can include name, email address, telephone number etc....

## How we Use the Information

If you contact us for any reason, we will use this information to respond to your inquiry. Also, unless you request not to, information may be sent to you to inform you of contests, promotions, discounts, and software updates or changes. 

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are commonly used throughout the web and are used on the DriverSleuth.com website. A cookie is a small piece of text data placed on your hard drive by DriverSleuth.com's servers to better serve our visitors and customers. Use of cookies have no way to determine the identity of the visitor. Cookies are harmless and cannot access your computer or place malicious software on your PC. Most browsers enable you to allow or disallow cookies when you visit a website. Driversleuth.com uses getclicky.com standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of our website visitors and trends. We also use conversion tracking package from google adwords to track downloads/leads/sales from our visitors with a 30 day tracking cookie. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site. We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site. 

## Links to External Websites

Throughout our site there are links to external websites, mainly manufacturer's drivers and download pages as a listed resource. These websites are not controlled by us in any way and we are not responsible for the privacy policy or actions of any other website other than Driversleuth.com. Please review their Terms of Use and Privacy Policies when viewing external sites. 

## Registration and Personal Info

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. However, this site may make forums, blogs, message boards or similar available to its users. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments or provide articles. If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent. 

Note: Driver Sleuth allows you to scan your PC for missing, outdated, and corrupt drivers at no charge. Registration of the software is $29.95 USD for a 1-year license which gives you full access to our driver database!

## Security

DriverSleuth takes appropriate security measures to ensure your data and information if collected is safe and secure. We use standard internet technologies to keep your data from intruders and unwanted access.

## Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website. 

## Contact Details

EMAIL: support[at]driversleuth.com  
DriverSleuth.com  
5607 Vanderbilt Ave.  
Dallas TX  
USA  
ENTIRE AGREEMENT 

Last updated on 09-17-2011.
